Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series I: Internal Structure and Units, 1936-1978, 1
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Apprenticeship Training Program materials, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Booster Club (fund-raiser for convention delegation), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Bureau of National Affairs, White Collar Report on AFTE, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Christmas mailing list, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Civil Defense speaker from city department, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Alfreida Clark (union bookkeeper) includes misuse of funds, 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: John R. Commons Research Library requesting the Bulletin, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Communist Party, USA: brochure and JLR's request to be removed from mailing list, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Congress of Racial Equality (CORE): invitation to James Farmer to speak to local., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Congressional Record reprints on labor bills, Iron Curtain, union label, etc. (Senators Lehman, Humphrey..), 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Construction jobs information, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Construction Superintendent Certificate, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Contract and committee lists, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: requests collective bargaining records, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Corps of Engineers (US Army), job vacancies, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Dies Committee (Congress) on "Communist infiltration" in CIO; Local 66's checklist [See also Rival union FAECT], 1944 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: 25th anniversary Dinner Dance, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Dinner dance, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Dodge Reports on job openings and applicants, 1950, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Draughtsmen's and Allied Technicians' Association: British activists (DATA issues placed in Tamiment vertical file), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 19a)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: President Eisenhower: letter to him on economy, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Employment information - West Coast, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Excavation and Foundation Contractors' Association dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Federal Meditation and Conciliation Service, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Foreign Operations Administration - office of labor affairs correspondence, for visit of French engineers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Foreign Operations Administration - office of labor affairs correspondence, for visit of French engineers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: French, Fink and Markle (attorneys) - re: Corbetta and Cement League strike cases, 1951, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: William J. Graves, organizer: hiring and dismissal, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Sen. Irving M. Ives: correspondence on economy, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Job inquiries for union staff positions, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Charles Keller and Co.: landlord, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Robert F. Kennedy, Sen-elect, autographed thank-you, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Frank Kornacker, engineer: letter from assistant, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Labor Features Syndicate, advertising catalog, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Gerald Lawrence, engineer, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Senator Herbert Lehman: letter on economy, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: correspondence to individuals, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: distribution of union tie clasps, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: eligibility list for election, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: election lists and data, 1959, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: election lists and data, 1959, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: excused absences (from meetings), 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: oath of obligation for new members, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: rate increase survey and constitution receipts, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Membership: Resumes for engineering jobs, 1959, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Robert Mozer, atty.: legal advice, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Mullikin Iron Lungs: fundraising for donation of iron lung, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Richard J. Narducci, atty., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: National Labor Relations Board: brochure, correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York Cancer Committee: brochure, correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York City: correspondence to various offices, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York City: economic cooperation award, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York State Board of Mediation, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York State Commission against discrimination: notice, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York State Department of Labor: for statistics, 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: New York State Labor Relations Board (SLRB) regulations, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Newsclippings re: Goldwater, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Radio broadcasts: prepared speeches and notes (JLR), 1944,47 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: J. Lawrence Raimist: personal data and days worked (taxes), 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: J. Lawrence Raimist: speeches at colleges; includes notes, 1947-1956 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Rand School of Social Science: letters, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Sidney Raphael, atty.: correspondence, 1947-1962 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Red Cross fundraising letter, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Rehabilitation Center for the Disabled fundraising letter, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Henry Sasch, member: donations to his blood bank, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Dinah Schleir, union employee fired, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Vim. F. Schnitzler testimonial dinner correspondence, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Seaman's Church Institute of NY: use of hall, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Subversive organizations (Dept. of Justice lists), 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: President Harry S. Truman: letters to him re Hungary, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: US Bronze Sign Co.: plaque for John P. Jones, retiring president, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. HEW/Social Security Administration for speaker, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. Department of Labor: press releases, 1939-1951, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. Department of Labor: circulars on statistics, 1948-1955 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. Department of the Navy: engineering classifications, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. Treasury Department: on taxes, 1957, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: U.S. Wage Stabilization Board: correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Business Manager Correspondence: Unity House resort, 1950, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Business Manager Files: Correspondence, notes on shops, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Business Manager Files: Correspondence, notes on shops, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Business Manager Files: Correspondence, notes on shops, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Business Manager Files: Correspondence, notes on shops, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Business Manager Files: Newsclippings on union wages, recent labor demands, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Business Manager Files: Reprints (nonlabor sources) on engineers and negotiations, Undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: J. Lawrence Raimist, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: William Evans, May-65 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Charles Hall, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports:, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports:, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and R. Morton, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Business Manager Weekly Reports: Ed Meskin and Ray Shannon, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To Executive Board, 1953, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To shop stewards, 1951-1958 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To members, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To members, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To members, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To employers, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To technical employees, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Circulars from Local 66: To members and shop stewards, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Committees: Committee lists, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Contract committee meeting notices, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Education committee meeting notice, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Education and legislation committees minutes (Rymer), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Education programs on "Dynamics of union leadership", 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Education: AFTE leadership training institute at Rutgers, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Grievance committee of the Executive Board: various cases, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Grievance committee of the Executive Board: various cases, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Grievance committee: charges against OIB officers; minutes, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Grievance committee: charges against business manager, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Nominating committee: nomination forms, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Organizing: Literature (ARMA and other shops), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Organizing: Leaflets, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Organizing: Weekly reports by organizer John T. Sinski (see also 4/35), 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Organizing: Leads, including laid-off members, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Organizing: Circulars to employees, examples from other unions, ca. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Organizing: Yonkers: background data on city budget, jobs, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Organizing: Pennsylvania and New Jersey: circulars including anti-AFTE, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Organizing: Report of firms handbilled, by John O'Leary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Organizing: Leads submitted by members, OIB, marble, heating, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Organizing: Organizing campaign: cards, correspondence, notes, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Organizing: Organizing campaign: cards, correspondence, notes, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Organizing: Organizing drive: construction timekeepers; notes, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Organizing: Organizing committee: notice, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Organizing: Correspondence on job shops, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Organizing: Pennsylvania correspondence and notes, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Organizing: Leads, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Organizing: Circulars, ca. 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Organizing: Architectural firms: NLRB materials, organizing meeting, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Ornamental Iron and Bronze (OIB): Summary of policies based on Local 66 minutes, 1923-1949 (predating affiliation with the IFTEAD), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - OIB: Meetings: financial reports, notices, attendance, 1944-1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - OIB: Meetings: financial reports, notices, attendance, 1944-1964 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - OIB: Meetings: financial reports, notices, attendance, 1944-1964 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - OIB: Minutes of employees meetings, with attendance sheets, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - OIB: Minutes, with related correspondence and reports, 1944-1949 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - OIB: Minutes, with attachments, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - OIB: Minutes, with attachments, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - OIB: Negotiations: includes steering committee minutes and JLR's last correspondence in service to Local 66, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - OIB: Negotiations: includes steering committee minutes and JLR's last correspondence in service to Local 66, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - OIB: Negotiations: includes steering committee minutes and JLR's last correspondence in service to Local 66, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - OIB: Negotiations: includes steering committee minutes and JLR's last correspondence in service to Local 66, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - OIB: Negotiations: includes steering committee minutes and JLR's last correspondence in service to Local 66, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - OIB: Negotiations: strike threat, copy of Cornell contract, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - OIB: Contracts, various shops (General Bronze, Hygrade, Ment), 1954-1972 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - OIB: Contracts, various shops (General Bronze, Hygrade, Ment), 1954-1972 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - OIB: Dinner dance: invitations and form letters, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - OIB: Reports and special letters, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - OIB: Clambake: lists, cartoon of those attending, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - OIB: Membership data: fines for non-attendance, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Other Divisions: HOLLOW METAL minutes, 1963 negotiations, correspondence and Evan's report on a stronger future without JLR and the "obstacle of the individual vs. the membership", 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Other Divisions: HOLLOW METAL minutes, 1963 negotiations, correspondence and Evan's report on a stronger future without JLR and the "obstacle of the individual vs. the membership", 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Other Divisions: HONESDALE (Penn.) minutes of Yuba employees meetings, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Other Divisions: OIL REFINERY and CHEMICAL PLANTS minutes, 1950-1964 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Other Divisions: OIL REFINERY and CHEMICAL PLANTS minutes, 1950-1964 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Other Divisions: RICHMOND minutes (see also Shop: S.S. White Dental), 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Wagner-Steagull Housing Bill, text: major effort by 66, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Amendment to Labor Law for technical employees, text and Local 66 minutes, 1937-1942 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Condon Wadlin Bill suspends benefits to strikers, 1948and67 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Public Housing Act, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Resolutions to U.S. Congressmen and Senators, 1949-1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Senate Bills (State of New York), 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Milmoe Bill on corporate engineering practice, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Welfare and Pension Funds, telegrams, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, text, AFTE analysis, brochures, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: New Jersey State Disability Law, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Advocacy Correspondence: Sen. Jacob K. Javits on compulsory arbitration, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Series II: Records of the International Union, 1936-1978, 2
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU) Chartering Local 66; FAECT bid for affiliation and charges of its "communist" domination; WPA workers, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU) 39-page report on employers by JLR (International v.p.), 1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU) Organizing assistance from international, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU then AFTE) Special memoranda and circulars, 1949-1957 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU then AFTE) -- Oct.1950 on right-wing CIO union; 1951 jurisdictional dispute, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFTEADU then AFTE) -- Oct.1950 on right-wing CIO union; 1951 jurisdictional dispute, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with the International (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Congressional voting records (JLR chairs AFTE Labor League for Political Education) (see also 10/2), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) federal locals; conflicts with carpenters union, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) federal locals; conflicts with carpenters union, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Texas organizing campaign and anti-communist note, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Texas organizing campaign and anti-communist note, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes complaints against v.p. Bechtel; "why unionize" report by International president; AFL-CIO merger, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes complaints against v.p. Bechtel; "why unionize" report by International president; AFL-CIO merger, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes complaints against v.p. Bechtel; "why unionize" report by International president; AFL-CIO merger, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes complaints against v.p. Bechtel; "why unionize" report by International president; AFL-CIO merger, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda and circulars, 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda and circulars, 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda and circulars, 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda and circulars, 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Contract file memos (mimeographed), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Engineering Association at Sperry Gyroscope and Charlie Hall of IUE (see also Shop file), 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Problems with IUE and IUD on organizing World's Fair employees (dual unionism), 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Retirees' honorary membership cards, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE), 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE), 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Local 66 representation with Local 113's area, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) Protesting appointment of Ross as secy/treas., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda, lack of organizing, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda, lack of organizing, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence with the International: (AFTE) includes special memoranda, lack of organizing, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence with the International: (IFPTE) legislation, convention resolutions, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (AFTE) Executive Council minutes, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (AFTE) Executive Council minutes, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (AFTE) Executive Council minutes, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (AFTE) Executive Council minutes, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (AFTE) Executive Council minutes, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: (IFPTE) Executive Council minutes of meeting, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Apprenticeship Committee correspondence and recommendations, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Legislative conference minutes, 1951, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 52)